Romance & Cigarettes is a comedy, music, romance film directed by John Turturro.
Ironworker Nick lives with his wife, Kitty, and three daughters.
When he meets a significantly younger woman, Tula, he starts an affair with her,
much to the chagrin of his wife, and his life is thrown into upheaval.
Kitty kicks Nick out of the house, and he is forced
to make some difficult decisions.
Nick Murder, played by James Gandolfini.
Kitty Kane, played by Susan Sarandon.
Tula, played by Kate Winslet.
Angelo, played by Steve Buscemi.
Fryburg, played by Bobby Cannavale.
Baby, played by Mandy Moore.
Romance & Cigarettes is a 2005 American musical romantic
comedy film written and directed by John Turturro.
The film stars an ensemble cast which includes James Gandolfini, Susan Sarandon, Kate Winslet, Steve Buscemi, Bobby Cannavale, Mandy
Moore, Mary-Louise Parker, Aida Turturro, Christopher Walken, Barbara Sukowa, Elaine Stritch, Eddie Izzard, and Amy Sedaris.
The film was nominated for a Golden Lion at the 2005 Venice Film Festival.
The film explores themes of infidelity, new york city, lovers, working class.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.